Guide to the Jerome H. Holland papers, 1953-1985
Holland, Jerome H. papers, 1953-1985
- Series IV. Sweden (Embassy)
  - Sweden, June 1971 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, June 1971 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Sweden, July 1971 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Sweden, July 1971 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Sweden, July 1971 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Sweden, July 1971 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Sweden, July 1971 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Sweden, July 1971 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Sweden, July 1971 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Sweden, July 1971 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Sweden, July 1971 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Sweden, August 1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Sweden, August 1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, August 1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, September 1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, September 1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Sweden, September 1971 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, September 1971 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, September 1971 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Sweden, October 1971 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, October 1971 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Sweden, October 1971 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, October 1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Sweden, October 1971 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, October 1971 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, November 1971 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, November 1971 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Sweden, November 1971 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Sweden, November 1971 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Sweden, November 1971 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Sweden, November 1971 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, November 1971 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Sweden, November 1971 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Sweden, December 1971 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Sweden, December 1971 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Sweden, December 1971 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Sweden, December 1971 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Sweden, December 1971 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Sweden, December 1971 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Sweden, December 1971 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Sweden: Planners, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Sweden: Clippings, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Sweden: Clippings, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Sweden: Clippings, May-September 1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Sweden: Clippings, October-December 1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, January 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Sweden, January 1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, January 1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, January 1972 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Sweden, January 1972 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, January 1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Sweden, January 1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, January 1972 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Sweden, February 1972 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, February 1972 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, February 1972 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, February 1972 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Sweden, February 1972 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Sweden, February 1972 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Sweden, February 1972 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Sweden, February 1972 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, February 1972 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Sweden, February 1972 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Sweden, March 1972 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Sweden, March 1972 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Sweden, March 1972 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Sweden, March 1972 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Sweden, March 1972 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Sweden, April 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Sweden, April 1972 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, April 1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, April 1972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, April 1972 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Sweden, April 1972 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, April 1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, May 1972 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Sweden, May 1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, May 1972 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Sweden, May 1972 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, May 1972 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Sweden, May 1972 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, June 1-15, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, June 1-15, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, June 1-15, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Sweden, June 1-15, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Sweden, June 1-15, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Sweden, June 1-15, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Sweden, June 16-30, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, June 16-30, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Sweden, June 16-30, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Sweden, June 16-30, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Sweden, June 16-30, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Sweden, June 1972 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Sweden, June 1972 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Sweden, June 1972 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Sweden, June 1972 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Sweden, July 1972 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Sweden, July 1972 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Sweden, July 1972 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Sweden, July 1972 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Sweden, July 1972 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Sweden, July 1972 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Sweden, July 1972 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Sweden, July 1972 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Sweden, August 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Sweden, August 1972 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, August 1972 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, August 1972 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, August 1972 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Sweden, August 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, August 1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, August 1972 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Sweden, August 1972 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, September 1972 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Sweden, October 1972 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, November 1972 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Sweden, November 1972 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, December 1972 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, December 1972 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, December 1972 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Sweden: Clippings, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Sweden: Clippings, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Sweden: Clippings, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Sweden: Planners, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, 1973-1982 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Sweden, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Sweden, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Sweden, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Sweden: Articles, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Sweden: Swedish Language, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Sweden: Photographs, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Series V. Photographs
  - Photographs, 1936-1974 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, 1975-1983 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, 1970-1981, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Photo Album:1984 ARMDI International Humanitarian Award, Item #1 (Box 34)
  - Photo Album: Union Carbide, 1979; Item #2 (Box 34)
  - Photo Album: Union Carbide, 1980; Item #3 (Box 34)
  - Photo Album: Salvation Army Association of New York, 1968; Item #4 (Box 34)
- Series VI. Miscellaneous
  - Account book - "Funds under the Administration of the President of Delaware State College", 1955-1960 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Audiotape: Jerome Holland press conference, Jan.13, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Chrysler Independence Day, August 15, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Honorary Degree: Virginia Union University, May 6, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Certificates, 1960-1963 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Certificates, 1970-1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Certificates, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Citations, 1970, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Honorary Degrees, 1966-1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Honorary Degrees, 1973-1981 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Planner, 1984-January 1985 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Resolution: Delaware State Education Association, May 26, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Swedish American Press and the Vietnam War, Edward Burton, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook: National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1970; Item #5 (Box 34)
  - Scrapbook: Cornell Class of 1939, Item #6 (Box 34)
  - Scrapbook: Delaware Principals Association, 1960; Item #7 (Box 34)
  - Scrapbook: Black Afro-American Newspapers, 1972; Item #8 (Box 34)
  - Scrapbook: Jerome H. Holland, 1972-1973; Item #9 (Box 34)
  - Scrapbook: Jerome H. Holland, 1979-1983; Item #10 (Box 34)
  - Scrapbook: Hollands at Hampton, 1960; Item #1 (Box 35)
  - Scrapbook: Hollands at Hampton, 1961-1962; Item #2 (Box 35)
  - Scrapbook: Hollands at Hampton, 1962; Item #3 (Box 35)
  - Scrapbook: Hampton-Goodbye letters and poems from children, Item #4 (Box 35)
  - Certificate: Cornell University Presidential Councillor, May 31, 1984; Item #5 (Box 35)
  - Certificate: Honorary Citizen of Dallas, TX, September 6, 1980; Item #6 (Box 35)
  - 1938 Cornellian, Item #7 (Box 35)
  - 1939 Cornellian, Item #8 (Box 35)
  - Certificate: Dover, Delaware Honorary Citizen, October 25, 1970; Item #1 (Box 36)
  - Certificate: Honorary Citizen, City and County of Honolulu, March 13, 1980; Items #2 (Box 36)
  - Certificate: National Geographic Society, June 9, 1977; Item #3 (Box 36)
  - Certificate: Virginia Cultural Development Study Commission, May 31, 1966; Item #4 (Box 36)
  - Charles Evans Hughes Award: National Conference of Christians and Jews, March 2, 1958; Item #5 (Box 36)
  - Citation of Merit: Salvation Army of New York, December 4, 1968; Item #6 (Box 36)
  - Collage: Thomas Edison, n.d.; Item #7 (Box 36)
  - Freedom Citation: Chapel of Four Chaplains, March 2, 1958; Item #8 (Box 36)
  - Honorary Degree: Eastern Michigan University, December 10, 1972; Item #9 (Box 36)
  - Honorary Degree: Hobart and William Smith Colleges, October 16, 1965; Item #10 (Box 36)
  - Honorary Degree: University of Cincinnati, June 10, 1966; Item #11 (Box 36)
  - UNCF: Salute to Hampton Institute, June 21, 1969; Item #12 (Box 36)
  - Watercolor: Davis Gray, NJ, n.d.; Item #13 (Box 36)
  - Award: CASE, Distinguished Service in Higher Education, July 8, 1980; Items #1 (Box 37)
  - Brotherhood Citation: National Conference of Christians and Jews, February 10, 1970; Items #2 (Box 37)
  - Certificate: American Academy of Arts and Sciences Membership, May 14, 1969; Items #3 (Box 37)
  - Certificate: Fairleigh Dickinson University, Rector and President, Items #4 (Box 37)
  - Certificate: President Richard Nixon's Appointment of Jerome H. Holland as Ambassador to Sweden, February 16, 1970; Items #5 (Box 37)
  - Certificate: United Supreme Council of Freemasons, Grand Inspector General, May 9, 1966; Items #6 (Box 37)
  - Degree: Cornell University, Bachelor of Science, June 19, 1939; Items #7 (Box 37)
  - Horary Degree: Colgate University, Items #8 (Box 37)
  - Honorary Degree: University of Pennsylvania, May 21, 1973; Items #9 (Box 37)
  - Nameplate: New York Stock Exchange, July 1972-May 1980; Items #10 (Box 37)
  - National Citation: Monroe County Human Relations Commission, June 7, 1976; Items #11 (Box 37)
  - Resolution: Culbro Corporation, Condolences and Appreciation, January 22, 1985; Items #12 (Box 37)
  - Resolution: Delaware Senate Appointment as Ambassador to Sweden, March 24, 1970; Items #13 (Box 37)
  - Resolution: New York Stock Exchange, May 1, 1980; Items #14 (Box 37)
  - Scrapbook: Football Hall of Fame, 1965; Items #1 (Box 38)
  - Scrapbook: Delaware St. College, 1957-1960; Items #1 (Box 39)
  - Scrapbook: Hollands at Hampton, 1964; Items #2 (Box 39)
  - Scrapbook: "Brud" since marriage, 1948-1957; Items #1 (Box 40)
  - Scrapbook, 1966; Items #2 (Box 40)
  - Scrapbook: Appointment as President of Hampton Institute, 1960; Items #1 (Box 41)
  - Plaques and Miscellaneous items, 1958-1983 (Box 42-51)
  - Newspaper Photos, and Diary, 1930-1940 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Diary, Pictures, 1953-1973 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, 1970-1973 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Palme, 1970-1980 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Misc., 1970-1979 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Misc., 1980's (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Get Well Cards, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Obituaries and Services, Tributes, Newspapers, et. al., 1985 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Telegrams, Flowers, Phone Calls, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Condolence Letters, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Memorial Contributions, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Tributes, Resolutions, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Cornell-Holland International Scholarship Fund Center, 1985-2004 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Holland International Center, 1985-1990 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Articles, Letters, etc., 1986-1999 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Red Cross Holland Laboratory, 1987-2004 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Passports, 1957-1982 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - American Red Cross Holland Laboratory, 1916-1985 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Club of New York: Charcoal drawing of Jerome H. Holland, December 7, 1965 (Map-case K AA-14)
  - Honorary Degree: Rider College, June 6, 1971 (Map-case K AA-14)
  - Honorary Degree: Washington & Lee University, June 4, 1971 (Map-case K AA-14)
  - Honorary Degree: Columbia University, June 6, 1972 (Map-case K AA-14)
  - Scrapbook: Clippings on appointment as Swedish ambassador, Jan.-Mar. 1970 (Volume I)
  - Scrapbook: Congratulations on appointment as Swedish ambassador, Jan. 1970 (Volume II)